Mobile Suit
Rage on! Rage on! Rage on! Gundam!
Moeagare! Moeagare! Moeagare GANDAMU!
You must run forth!
Kimi yo hashire
If you are still burning with furious rage...
Mada ikari ni moeru toshi ga aru nara...
You must fight the towering foe!
Kyodai na teki o
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Uteyo! Uteyo! Uteyo!
Bring to bear the rage of justice, Gundam
Seigi no ikari o butsukero GANDAMU
Mobile Suit Gundam! Gundam!
Kidou senshi GANDAMU! GANDAMU!
Rise once more! Rise once more!
Yomigaeru! Yomigaeru!
Rise once more! Gundam!
Yomigaeru GANDAMU!
You must seize the power!
Kimi yo tsukame
Fly toward the galaxy, Gundam!
Ginga e mukatte tobeyo GANDAMU
Mobile Suit Gundam! Gundam!
Kidou senshi GANDAMU! GANDAMU!
The three Musais led by Lieutenant Dren
waited in the White Base's path...
...but were eliminated by the Gundam.
The White Base then set
a course for Side 6.
However...
Farewell in Side Six
This region was once the site of Side 1.
Now it is the location of Solomon,
headquarters of the Space Attack Force...
...commanded by Vice Admiral Dozle Zabi.
The Conscon Mobile Unit
is about to be deployed.
Vice Admiral Dozle was displeased that
his sister Kycilia was using Char's services.
He wished he could personally destroy the
Trojan Horse and prove Char's incompetence.
However...
...until he discovered the objectives
of the Tianem Fleet assembling at Luna II...
...he could not afford to send out
any more military power.
What do you think, Ms. Sayla?
Nothing unusual, is there?
Yes, everything seems to be normal.
But there are so many rocks here,
it's hard to say...
Kai! Do you read? What's up?
No problems! But I've got low
fuel reserves, so I'm heading back.
I'd like us to patrol a bit longer
in the G-Armor. Is that okay?
That's fine.
It'll give me a chance to learn more
about the navigation.
Hey, Amuro.
How do you feel about Fraw Bow?
Huh? Why do you ask?
Why? Because you've been
rather cold toward her lately.
That's not true...
Oh really?
Friendships are important in times like these.
It's not like I hate her or something...
Portside!
What?
They've spotted us.
We should attack.
Hold off a bit longer.
They had to come during a malfunction!
Are the engines working?
Somehow.
Oh no! Ms. Sayla, get back!
What?
They're firing at us!
It's a Zeon mobile armor!
I-I'm not so sure it's a mobile armor...
Here it comes!
You fool! Why did you shoot?!
They were coming to attack us!
That's not what they intended! Careless fool!
This mobile armor's unusual!
Let's go behind the rock so we can bolt out!
Roger!
I've overpowered the engine!
Never mind that!
The enemy has seen our Braw-Bro,
so we must destroy them.
3... 2... 1...
Over there!
Just one enemy... Let's finish him!
The attacks are coming from odd angles.
Be careful!
Roger!
Where are those shots coming from?!
If that's their fastest speed...
There!
And we were so close
to deploying it in combat.
That took some time, Amuro.
We should return to the White Base
before it enters Side 6 airspace.
Roger!
Within these beacons
lies Side 6 airspace.
Here, the forces of both
Zeon and the Earth Federation...
...are prohibited from all warfare.
Welcome aboard.
I'm Cameron Bloom,
Side 6 Prosecutor.
We've sealed all the White Base's
missile launchers, guns, and beam cannons.
If even one of them is broken...
Yes, I do understand.
If that happened, we'd pay a very stiff fine.
Yes.
I'd like to ask you about our ship's repairs...
We won't be able to do that within Side 6.
It would be considered assisting the war.
Allow me to take you to the bridge.
Ms. Sayla?
That attack definitely came from somewhere
other than the mobile armor, right?
We weren't just seeing things.
Can't you figure it out?
No. Amuro must have encountered
some new mobile armor.
I see.
Perfect timing. We're about to enter port.
Fine.
Approach angle good.
Entry speed 05.
Entering Side 6's Palda Bay!
All hands, prepare for docking!
Laser sensors open 360 degrees!
Mirai! It's you, Mirai!
Cameron! Why are you here?
Mirai! You made it through alive! M-Mirai!
I'm glad you're well.
Who is that?
A relative?
Mr. Cameron.
We're in the middle of docking.
Please restrain yourself.
You too, Ensign Mirai.
Oh. Right... Beg your pardon, Lieutenant.
Mirai.
I'm so happy. I'd given up all hope
of ever seeing you again.
Then this war broke out.
If your father hadn't passed away,
we might've avoided the war.
Yes, you're right...
Then I might not have
had to emigrate to Side 7 either.
That's just it.
Why didn't you let me know, Mirai?!
I was desperate to find out where you were!
Desperate...?
Yes. I had people look for you everywhere.
You wouldn't believe how much I spent.
I see...
So why didn't you look
for me yourself?
I was busy emigrating here
to Side 6 around that time.
Our engagement was merely to please
our parents, wasn't it...
That's not true, Mirai!
You've got it all wrong.
Won't you come home with me?
Father will be so thrilled!
What? But I...
You won't regret it.
Mirai, I'd do anything for you!
Slow down a bit!
Excuse me.
I hate seeing a guy harassing a lady.
Lieutenant Sleggar, I'm fine!
Are you sure?
Yes!
You heard the lady.
Hey, Mr. Fancypants! Here you go!
Have your glasses back.
Oh...!
Cameron. Are you okay?
Yeah. It seems I don't know how
to court a lady properly. Right, Lieutenant?
Precisely.
After all, Ensign Mirai's like a mother
to all of us on the White Base.
One moment you're serving
under Vice Admiral Dozle...
...and the next, you serve
under Rear Admiral Kycilia.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
How many times have you allowed
the Trojan Horse to escape? Honestly!
Why don't I show you how it's done!
Watch and learn something.
Yes, sir!
Who told you that you were dismissed?!
Please don't bully your juniors.
I'll happily observe you in action, sir.
Why doesn't he ever remove that mask?
Allegedly it's a terrible burn...
But some rumors say he's quite handsome.
I'll strip that wolf of his sheepskin one day.
How's the Rick Dom team
that infiltrated around Palda Bay?
Sir! As of yet, they haven't been discovered,
even by Side 6's patrol ships.
Excellent.
Mulligan...
Send an encrypted message
to Rear Admiral Kycilia from the Zanzibar.
Sir!
"Pararom Zu, Char." Got it?
Is that all?
Don't ask any questions.
It's classified.
Mr. Tamura. Did you exchange your money?
Yeah. No problem.
We're moving!
The center of this artificial space-city...
...is a zero-gravity zone,
where one experiences weightlessness.
From here, an elevator descends
over 3000 meters...
...to artificial ground
where one can feel one's own weight.
Mountains, forests, and rivers
have been formed there...
...to create a landscape
much like that of Earth.
Naturally, a modern city has also been built.
- Wow! This is great!
- This is amazing!
Finally, I can change up the menu a bit.
F-Father...!
Mobile Suit
Gundam
What's wrong, Amuro?
You guys go on ahead!
I'm gonna check out that bookstore there.
Dad!
Oh... it's you, Amuro.
So how's the Gundam faring in battle?
Is it doing well?
Uh, yes...
Dad...!
Come with me.
Sure.
What are you waiting for?! Come in!
What is this place?
The thing about junkyards is...
...they're ideal for intelligence gathering.
I've been living here lately...
I want you to install this
in the Gundam's memory circuits.
I developed it based on the circuits
from Zeon mobile suits.
It's practically an antique!
He's suffering from oxygen deficiency.
It's amazing. It'll increase the Gundam's
combat abilities several times over.
Take it!
Install this and test it right away.
Y-Yes, I will. But what about you, Dad?
I have a lot of research to finish.
I'll be in touch again.
Now, hurry up and go!
Right.
Dad...
I saw Mom back home.
Dad!
Aren't you concerned about how Mom is?
Hm? Yes. The war will be over soon.
Once it's finished, let's visit the Earth.
D-Dad...
Dad...
Get going! You're a soldier now!
Amuro. I don't recall giving you permission
to wander around the city on your own.
Our departure's been delayed, thanks to you.
I'm sorry, sir.
But we're leaving so suddenly...
Escort the White Base out in the Gundam.
Mr. Bergamino.
Yes?
You're sure that's what
Prosecutor Cameron Bloom requested?
Yes. I got a video call from the Prime
Minister's residence. There's no mistake.
If the dock's located outside the airspace...
...we're permitted to repair any vessel,
whether Zeon or Federation.
We're being pursued. Will it really be safe...?
Not to worry!
I do have connections
with the top brass on both sides.
Young lady, you have no need to worry.
Thank you, Mr. Bergamino.
Yo, Amuro. You feeling okay now?
Always was.
Is that so? Glad to hear it. That's a good boy.
Mr. Sleggar.
What is it?
Could you please
put a lid on that "good boy" stuff?
Sure. Sorry 'bout that.
I've got something...
Hey! Looks like the Trojan Horse!
How kind of them to come out on their own!
Is that the floating dock?
What's that?
A signal flare from Kayahawa?!
That means the Trojan Horse
has left Side 6 airspace!
Confirm its position!
Engines to maximum!
Why did the Trojan Horse leave so quickly?
Position confirmed!
They're at Bergamino's floating dock!
Bergamino?!
That war profiteer.
This is perfect.
The enemy is directly
in our fleet's line of fire...
Launch 12 Rick Doms!
Conscon has detected the Trojan Horse?
Yes, apparently.
They've launched their Rick Doms.
This is huge...
What?!
Damn! Is this a trap?!
No! Not my precious dock!
Bright! Cameron isn't
the kind of person who'd do that!
Hard to starboard!
All units, hurry up and launch!
L-Lieutenant! Please keep your ship
away from my dock!
Then my precious dock will be saved!
We're doing that!
The suits with skirts!
One down! Next?!
That's three!
Target the ship in the center! Fire!
The enemy managed to destroy the Kwamel?!
The Doms?!
How are the Rick Doms doing?
Don't let up on your attack!
Isn't that where Bergamino's
floating dock is located?
Yes, sir.
How did Zeon find out?
We must stop them from fighting now.
We can't let any of their stray beams
enter Side 6 airspace.
Five!
Six!
Why you...!
Eight!
Nine!
All of them were destroyed?
All 12 Rick Doms were destroyed?!
Wiped out in under 3 minutes?!
Y-Yes, sir!
We've lost 12 Rick Doms
to one badly damaged warship...
It's some kind of monster!
It's the Zanzibar!
It's Char! Has he come to laugh at me?!
The Zanzibar's approaching!
What?!
Bright! Let's retreat to Side 6!
Right! Order all machines to retreat
to Side 6!
But what about my dock...
My precious dock!
Don't attack!
That's a Side 6 patrol ship!
Tell Conscon's group to stop firing as well!
Hitting a patrol ship would start
an international incident!
Mr. Cameron!
Taking extra risks to stop a battle
isn't in my job description!
I know, I'm sorry.
But my future wife happens to be
aboard that Federation Forces ship.
Don't worry.
Father will cover up the fact
that you broke the weapon seals.
So...?
I mean... with Father's help
I can arrange for you to live here in Side 6.
That's not it.
If I'm supposed to abandon the White Base...
...what are you willing to do for me?
Like I've been saying...
I'll ask Father to help you.
You still don't understand anything...
If that's the case...
I can't abandon the White Base.
Mirai.
You would never have said
something like that before.
What is it that you want from me?
If it weren't for the war...
But you know... That's not it.
Cameron. You've done nothing but
escape from the war.
You haven't changed a bit.
I love you! That's something
I could never change, Mirai!
Thank you... That means a lot to me.
M-Mirai!
What is it that you don't like about me?!
Mirai! Tell me!
I'll try to change, if that's what you want!
Mirai!
A young girl, Lalah, predicts that
Amuro and Char will meet face to face.
Far from the battlefield,
the seeds of the next battle are sprouting.
Bearing many different destinies...
...the White Base launches into space
where the enemy awaits.
Mobile Suit Gundam. Next episode...
A Fateful Encounter
Next Time
Will you be able to survive?
Amuro, do not look back
The star shining far off in space...
Amuro, it's your homeland where you were born
Do you remember the days of your childhood?
The morning when you woke up in warmth?
Amuro, do not look back, Amuro...
A man must hide his tears, hide his tears
Only look to tomorrow, to tomorrow forever...